{
    "id": "4c8e34196726417ca80302933822eae9",
    "title": "Articles Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "If you are really hungry, you can eat ……………… apple.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "25f4e7afb31e4c67b8c6d11f10fe8889"
        },
        {
            "question": "She went on to become ………………….. successful playback singer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7d9033e530e1485fa3ccbf2154048ed8"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… library on the corner has an amazing collection of story books.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "A",
                "An",
                "The"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9886733792444ab2a30c6444915d4cb5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t speak ………………… Hindi very well, but I can make myself understood.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "No article is needed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "19369d4550b342b2b5f024e165b2cb92"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ………………… prettiest girl I have ever seen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "No article is needed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "691d5d27bdc741e4a86ea2ba77fc3f64"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Where is ………………… cheese?’ ‘I ate it.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "No article is needed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0b64f05cd02b4e4aae50bea408f1d453"
        },
        {
            "question": "Move ………………… books off that chair and sit down.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9b5c792e48074921bb2f9da33fa07c36"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… . Irish have their own language.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "An",
                "The",
                "No article is needed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dd30d1e8b4194d3bad53605b07cfef07"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. life is complicated.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "A",
                "The",
                "No article is needed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3adef9b6d1d54e18b8b401e6b1f0a33a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am writing ………………… book on Indian mythology.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1bb0f05ad8f64e33b0c0b6c8a0cfcfec"
        }
    ]
}